我们来看看设置界面画的线框图
Let's go through the wire frames for the settings UI.
在DetailActivity中的溢出项目菜单（overflow menu），有一个设置选项
Within the detail activity in the overflow menu, there's a settings menu item.
当你单击这个设置选项，会打开一个SettingsActivity
When you tap on the setting's menu item, it opens up the SettingsActivity.
如果你单击LOCATION(地点)项，会弹出一个对话框，你可以向这里面填入邮编
If you tap of location, it pops up a dialog, where you can enter in your
用你最习惯的方式去输入地点
postal code. Feel free to use your preferred method for inputting location,
比如说输一个城市名。只需确保从服务器端返回的数据
such as city name. Just verify that the data coming back from the server is for
是你所期望的。注意对这里的字符串输入是没有检验的
the location you expect. Note that there's no validation on this string input.
如果你想让这个App成为一个成品App，你应该在这里做一些对错误输入的处理
If you're trying to make this app a production app, you would want some kind of
如果你单击“PICK YOUR UNIT”(单位），会打开一个对话框
error handling here. If you tap on pick your units, it opens up a dialogue
你可以从中选择一个在这个APP里的温度按公制单位或英制单位显示
where you can choose to display temperature within the app as wither metric or
这里的话就是摄氏和华氏
imperial units. This is basically just Celsius or Fahrenheit, and
这就是SettingsActivity所做的。记住，你不会想将所有东西
that is what this SettingsActivity does. Remember that you don't want to make
都来个设置选项。如果你和组员一起讨论一个特性
everything a setting. If you're discussing a feature with a teammate and you
并且不知道怎么办才好，不要折衷地将它做成一个用户设置选项
can't decide on something, don't compromise by just making it a user setting.
有很多经验都表明，现在做一个艰难的产品决定会对用户比较好
There are instances where making a difficult product decision now will be better
因为这样用户就不需要担心不知道该设置什么值
for the user, because then they won't have the burden of having to decide what
并且记住，总是有下一次App升级的机会
the value of the setting should be. And remember, there's always an opportunity
去往里面添加新功能，所以要三思熟虑。如果你一开始就加了
in an app update to add the setting later. If you add it to begin with, it's
想再去掉某些设置是很困难的，因为那时候会激起有些用户的愤怒
infinitely harder to take away the setting because some users might get angry
如果你在决定是否应该添加一个设置项上犹豫不决
with you. If you're having trouble deciding if something should be a setting or
你可以看一下安卓设计指南中的“设置”小节
not, you can check out the setting section in the Android design guide,
在下方给出了链接。其中包含一个工作流程图，可能会帮到你
which is linked below. It contains a workflow diagram that could help you.
你会发现你应该尽可能的不要让用户去“设置”些什么
Very few roads often lead to making something a setting.